{
    "subject": "resource/Eyemart_Express",
    "predicate": "property/products",
    "object": "resource/Sunglasses",
    "human_readable": "Eyemart Express offers Sunglasses.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9786235094070435,
            "question": "Can you purchase Sunglasses at Eyemart Express?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9662480354309082,
            "question": "Does Eyemart Express sell Sunglasses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9057297110557556,
            "question": "Besides Sunglasses, what else might Eyemart Express sell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8464798927307129,
            "question": "What does Eyemart Express offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6430229544639587,
            "question": "What is an example of a product offered by Eyemart Express?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6214934587478638,
            "question": "What type of store is Eyemart Express?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5315316915512085,
            "question": "Eyemart Express specializes in what type of goods?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5250581502914429,
            "question": "Is Eyemart Express a retailer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.437765508890152,
            "question": "Name a product sold by Eyemart Express."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29966819286346436,
            "question": "Where could you buy Sunglasses from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eyemart Express offers Sunglasses.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1286_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a product sold by Eyemart Express.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1286_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Eyemart Express a retailer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1286_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eyemart Express specializes in what type of goods?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1286_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1286_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"Sunglasses\" several times, and it is clear that Eyemart Express offers a wide range of sunglasses for sale. The text even mentions specific features of their sunglasses, such as customizable tints and prescription lenses. Therefore, the statement that Eyemart Express offers Sunglasses is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context provided mentions that Eyemart Express offers a wide collection of customizable sunglasses, which supports the statement that Eyemart Express offers sunglasses."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}